bonqo.com 2011-11-01

# Bonqo: privacy_policy

Revised: May 24, 2010

## 1.0 Introduction

Your privacy is very important to us. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, protect, and disclose information and data when you use the Bonqo.com website ("Site") or any related services ("Services"). The Site and Services are owned and operated by ELLA Internet Technologies Inc. ("ELLA"). This Privacy Policy also explains your choices for managing your information preferences, including opting out of certain uses of your Personal Information. By using the Site or Services you consent to this Privacy Policy.

## 2.0 Managing Your Information Preferences

You can always review, correct, update, or change your Personal Information, or opt out of our direct marketing efforts, by changing the relevant settings in your Site profile or account (if available), or by e-mailing us at [support@bonqo.com](mailto:support@bonqo.com?subject=Personal%20Information). If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [feedback@bonqo.com](mailto:feedback@bonqo.com).

## 3.0 Information We Collect

#### 3.1 Personal Information.

We collect information that personally identifies you, such as your name, address, telephone number, username, e-mail, and other personally identifiable information that you choose to provide us with or that you choose to include in any Site profile or account ("Personal Information"). We collect Personal Information only if you choose to share it with us. You may be asked to provide us with Personal Information when you register with the Site or any of our Services, and at other times. The decision to provide this information is optional. However, if you choose not to provide the requested information, you may not be able to use certain features of the Site or Services.

#### 3.2 Usage Data.

We automatically collect anonymous usage information that does not identify an individual user ("Usage Data"). For example, each time you use the Site we automatically collect the type of Web browser you use, your operating system, your Internet Service Provider, your IP address, the pages you view, and the time and duration of your visits to the Site. We use this information to help us understand how people use the Site and Services, and to enhance the services we offer.

#### 3.3 Cookies and Web Beacons.

We use cookies (a small text file placed on your computer to identify your computer and browser). We also use Web beacons (an electronic file placed on a Website that monitors usage). We use cookies and Web beacons to improve the quality of the Site and Services. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your Web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, certain features of the Site or Services may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Some of our Service Providers may use their own cookies and Web beacons in connection with the services they perform on our behalf.

## 4.0 How We Use Information and When We May Share and Disclose Information.

#### 4.1 Generally.

We use Personal Information for internal purposes only, such as to provide you with the Site and Services, to notify you of new products or Services, and to otherwise communicate with you about our business. We will not disclose Personal Information to third parties without your consent, except as explained in this Privacy Policy.

#### 4.2 Profile Information You Make Available to Others.

By using the Site or the Services you may make certain of your Personal Information available to others. For example, when you post a classified advertisement on the Site other users may see your name, the city you live in and other information from your post that you choose to make available to others. The information you choose to make available, may be accessed by other Site users who conduct searches on the Site and may be accessed by commercial search engines such as Google, Yahoo!, and Bing to the extent that such engines are permitted to access the Site.

#### 4.3 Service Providers.

From time to time, we may establish a business relationship with other businesses whom we believe trustworthy and who have confirmed that their privacy practices are consistent with ours ("Service Providers"). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, such as hosting and maintenance, data storage and management, and marketing and promotions. We only provide our Service Providers with the information necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf. Each Service Provider must agree to use reasonable security procedures and practices, appropriate to the nature of the information involved, in order to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Service Providers are prohibited from using Personal Information other than as specified by us.

#### 4.4 Ad Networks.

We may work with third-party marketing and advertising companies ("Ad Networks"). These companies may collect and use information about your use of the Site or Services in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Advertisements may be shown via the Site, the Services, or third-party websites. These companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as Web beacons. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that an Ad Network may collect from you. It also does not cover any information that you may choose to provide to an Ad Network or to an advertiser whose goods or services are advertised through the Site or Services. For more information about ad cookies, and to "opt-out" of the collection of information by some companies that allow you to do so, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

#### 4.5 Standard Analytics Information.

We may use, and disclose to third parties, certain Usage Data regarding the Site and Services. However, in such cases, your Usage Data is aggregated with the Usage Data of other users and does not identify you individually.

#### 4.6 Other Transfers.

We may share Personal Information and Usage Data with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with ELLA. If ELLA is merged, acquired, or sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets, we may disclose or transfer Personal Information and Usage Data in connection with such transactions. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if, in our discretion, the new entity plans to handle your information in a way that differs materially from this Privacy Policy.

#### 4.7 Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement.

ELLA cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose Personal Information and any other information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it is necessary or appropriate in order to respond to legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas), to protect the safety, property or rights of ELLA or of any third party, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

## 5.0 Be Careful When You Share Information with Others.

Please be aware that whenever you share information on a publicly available profile page or any other public forum on the Site, that information may be accessed by others. In addition, when you share information in any other communications with third parties, that information may be passed along or made public by others. This means that anyone with access to such information can potentially use it for any purpose, including sending unsolicited communications.

## 6.0 Security

We recognize the importance of safeguarding the confidentiality of your Personal Information. Accordingly, we employ reasonable measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Site or Services, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through the Site or Services, and you do so at your own risk.

## 7.0 Links To Other Websites

Our Site and Services may contain links to other websites, or allow others to send you such links. A link to a third party's website does not mean that we endorse it or that we are affiliated with it. We do not exercise control over third-party websites. You access such third-party websites or content at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a third-party website before providing any information to the website.

## 8.0 Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. In addition, we recommend that minors 13 years of age or older ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

## 9.0 Privacy Policy Changes

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will inform you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Site. Those changes will go into effect on the Revision Date shown in the revised Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our Site or Services constitutes your consent to the revised Privacy Policy.
